A Guide to the Population Council records, Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) 1969-1971 Project Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 11 FA1431
Rockefeller Archive Center
Population Council records, Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) 1969-1971 Project Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 11
1967-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Population Council
FA1431
11.09 Cubic Feet 23 letter-size document boxes and 5 legal-size document boxes.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
This series contains Office of Economic Opportunity project files. Institutional grantees include, but are not limited to, Albert Einstein College of Medicine, Columbia University, Case Western Reserve University, Emory University, New York Medical College, Temple University, University of Chicago, University of Florida, and the University of Pennsylvania. Records include correspondence, proposals, reports, program files, evaluations, budgets, financial statements and audit reports.
Biographical / Historical
The Population Council was founded by John D. Rockefeller 3rd in 1952 to undertake "significant activities in the broad field of population." Its goal has been to bring about a reduction in the number of births that occur in the world. In its early years, the business of the Population Council was conducted by a Demographic Division and a Biomedical Division. Through its Demographic Division, the Council sought to document what it conceived to be an overpopulation problem threatening many areas of the world. To accomplish this purpose, the Division facilitated research on the economic, social, and psychological factors which affect the growth and decline of human population. This Council-assisted research effort was conducted not only by staff of the Demographic Division but also by other institutions and scholars, some of whom received Council grants and fellowships and some of whom received informal advice and consultation on how to design and execute studies.
The Biomedical Division, which, beginning in 1959, occupied a laboratory at The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (now The Rockefeller University), has conducted pure and applied research on plant, animal, and human reproductive physiology and on the development, the physiological action, and the safety and effectiveness of contraceptive methods. The Council facilitated similar types of medical research by non-Council scientists at other institutions by giving grants and fellowships for such research. The Council's biomedical research and its support for research by non-Council scientists were instrumental in the development of the modern intrauterine coil and the birth control pill.
In about 1960, the scope of Population Council activities expanded. The Council began to render practical and technical aid to foreign nations. Beginning in that year, the Demographic Division, in addition to supervising research, became involved in Pakistan's family planning program, extending practical and technical aid in organizing and running a national family planning program. By 1964 the Council's Demographic Division had assisted in organizing family planning programs in South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, Tunisia, and Turkey. In that year, the Council created the Technical Assistance Division. This division, in ensuing years, continued the assistance of the Council in the countries where it had already become involved and also helped start and run programs in India, Morocco, the Philippines, and Puerto Rico.
An underlying aim of the Council's grant programs has been to encourage the development and growth of institutions that would promote family planning programs. To this end, the Council has given grants and advice to various universities and research centers for starting and upgrading programs for demographic and biomedical training and research programs; has assisted the United Nations to set up and expand regional Demographic Training and Research Centres in Bombay, India, Santiago, Chile, and Cairo, Egypt; has worked with the Ford Foundation on family planning programs in Pakistan, India, and North Africa.
In addition to rendering technical aid and sponsoring research, the Council has undertaken several complementary public relations efforts. To reach the general populations of the United States and of foreign nations, Council officers have worked to inform the mass media about population issues and to encourage magazine articles, movies, and books dealing with population matters. Council officers and representatives have also made trips and prepared reports to convince various foreign government leaders of the importance and the desirability of promulgating family planning programs. In addition, Council officers participated in and helped organize and finance conferences for demographers and medical scientists active in population work.
The Population Council has obtained its financial support through large contributions. The Ford and Rockefeller Foundations and the Rockefeller Brothers Fund have been the principal institutional supporters of the Council. John D. Rockefeller 3rd has been the single most significant individual backer of the Council.
- University of Pennsylvania - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress (Box 1, Folder 4)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits (Box 1, Folder 5)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- University of Pennsylvania - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- University of Pennsylvania - A.1. - Correspondence - General (Box 1, Folder 10)
- University of Pennsylvania - A.2. - Proposal Year A (Box 3, Folder 39)
- University of Pennsylvania - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- University of Pennsylvania - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- University of Pennsylvania - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - A.3. - Agreement Year A (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Pittsburgh-Magee Womens Hospital - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Wayne State - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Wayne State - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Wayne State - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Wayne State - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Wayne State - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Wayne State - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Wayne State - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Wayne State - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Wayne State - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Wayne State - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Wayne State - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Wayne State - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Wayne State - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- West Virginia - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- West Virginia - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- West Virginia - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- West Virginia - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- West Virginia - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- West Virginia - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- West Virginia - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- West Virginia - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- West Virginia - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- West Virginia - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- West Virginia - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- West Virginia - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.5.d. - Financial - Budget Revisions, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - A.3. - Agreement Year 1, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Case Western Reserve - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Case Western Reserve - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Case Western Reserve - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Case Western Reserve - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Case Western Reserve - B.5.a. - Financial - Provincial Reports, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Case Western Reserve - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Case Western Reserve - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Case Western Reserve - B.5.d. - Financial - Budget Revisions, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Case Western Reserve - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Case Western Reserve - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Case Western Reserve - A.2. - Proposal Year 1, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Case Western Reserve - A.3. - Agreement Year 1, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Case Western Reserve - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Case Western Reserve - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.2. - Correspondence - General, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.5.d. - Financial - Budget Revisions, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - B.6. - Audit, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - A.2. - Proposal Year 1, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - A.3. - Agreement Year 1, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 93)
- Columbia - Harlem Hospital - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 94)
- Emory University - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 95)
- Emory University - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 96)
- Emory University - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 97)
- Emory University - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 98)
- Emory University - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 99)
- Emory University - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 100)
- Emory University - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 101)
- Emory University - B.5.d. - Financial - Budget Revisions, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 102)
- Emory University - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 103)
- Emory University - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 104)
- Emory University - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 105)
- Emory University - A.3. - Agreement Year 1, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 106)
- Emory University - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 107)
- Emory University - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports (Box 7, Folder 108)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 109)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 110)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 111)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress (Box 8, Folder 112)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 113)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports (Box 8, Folder 114)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 115)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 116)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.5.d. - Financial - Budget Revisions, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 117)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 118)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - A.1. - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 119)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 120)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - A.3. - Agreement Year 1, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 121)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress (Box 8, Folder 122)
- International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction (IISHR) - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 123)
- Johns Hopkins - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 124)
- Johns Hopkins - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 125)
- Johns Hopkins - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 126)
- Johns Hopkins - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 127)
- Johns Hopkins - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 128)
- Johns Hopkins - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 129)
- Johns Hopkins - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 130)
- Johns Hopkins - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 131)
- Johns Hopkins - B.6. - Audit Period B (Box 9, Folder 132)
- Johns Hopkins - A.2. - Proposal Year A, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 133)
- Johns Hopkins - A.3. - Agreement Year A, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 134)
- Johns Hopkins - A.4 - Reports - Program Progress, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 135)
- Johns Hopkins - A.5. - Payments and Financial Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 136)
- B.2. - Population Council Contract Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 137)
- B.2. - Population Council Contract Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 138)
- B.3. - Correspondence - Population Council to Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 139-140)
- B.4. - Correspondence - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) to Population Council, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 141)
- A.2. - Population Council Contract Program Period A, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 142)
- A.2. - Population Council Contract Program Period A, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 143)
- B.5. - Correspondence - Population Council to All Universities, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 144)
- B.7. - Internal Memos, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 145)
- B.8.a. - Conference - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 146)
- A.3. - Correspondence - Population Council to Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) (Box 11, Folder 147)
- A.4. - Correspondence - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) to Population Council, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 148)
- A.5. - Correspondence - Population Council to All Universities, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 149)
- A.8.a. - Conferences - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 150)
- B.8.b. - Conferences - Annual Meeting (Box 12, Folder 151)
- A.14. - Westinghouse Evaluation (Box 12, Folder 152)
- B.15. - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 153)
- A.12.b. - Financial Population Council Monthly Reports to Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 154)
- B.1. - Population Council Proposal Program Period B, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 155)
- A.8.b. - Conferences - Annual Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 156)
- A.9. - Project Advisory Board, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 157)
- A.10. - Audit, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 158)
- B.10. - Audit, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 159)
- Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 160)
- A.12.a. - Financial - Report Forms (Box 13, Folder 161)
- A.12.b. - Financial Population Council Monthly Reports to Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 162)
- A.12.b. - Financial Population Council Monthly Reports to Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 163)
- B.13.b. - Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 164)
- A.6. - Correspondence - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) to Universities (Box 13, Folder 165)
- A.7. - Internal Memos, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 166)
- A.1. - Population Council Proposal Program Period A (Box 13, Folder 167)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) - Manuals, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 168-170)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) - Medical Schools - General, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 171)
- A.18. - General Services Agency (GSA), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 172)
- B.19.b. - Population Council Evaluation (Box 15, Folder 173-175)
- B.19.b. - Population Council Evaluation (Box 16, Folder 176)
- B.19.c. - Population Council Evaluation - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 177)
- B.20. - Correspondence with American Public Health Association (APHA), 1971 (Box 16, Folder 178)
- Correspondence - Population Council General, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 179)
- Correspondence - Population Council Field Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 180)
- Correspondence - Population Council New York - Preparation and Consideration, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 181)
- Correspondence - NRE Fendall, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 182)
- Correspondence - NRE Fendall, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 183-184)
- Correspondence - NRE Fendall, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 207)
- Briefing papers - NRE Fendall, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 208)
- Drafts and Finals on Project Proposals (Box 17, Folder 185-187)
- Drafts and Finals on Project Proposals (Box 18, Folder 188-191)
- Drafts and Finals on Project Proposals (Box 19, Folder 192)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) - Forms (Box 19, Folder 193-195)
- Correspondence with Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 196)
- Early Correspondence - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 197)
- Early Correspondence - Universities, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 198)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) - Family Planning via Medical Schools Proposal - Early Drafts (Box 20, Folder 199-201)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Proposal - Historical Data, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 202)
- Early Drafts of Population Council Proposal, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 203)
- Population Council Forms (Box 21, Folder 204)
- 9. - Rejected Proposals (Box 21, Folder 205)
- 10. - Meetings, Conferences and Memos on Program, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 206)
- Memos - Population Council General, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 209-211)
- Reports - Population Council General, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 212)
- Reports - NREF Reports (Box 22, Folder 213)
- A.19. - Population Council Evaluation - Form A's (Box 22, Folder 214)
- A.19. - Population Council Evaluation - Form A's (Box 23, Folder 215-216)
- A.19.a. - Population Council Evaluation - Short Form, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 217)
- A.19.b. - Population Council Evaluation - Long Form (Box 23, Folder 218)
- A.19.b. - Population Council Evaluation - Long Form - Questionnaire Returned (Box 23, Folder 219)
- A.19.b. - Population Council Evaluation - Long Form - Questionnaire Returned (Box 24, Folder 220)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.1. - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 221)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.2. - Proposal Program Period B, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 222)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.3. - Contract Amendment Program Period B, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 223)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.4.a. - Reports - Program Progress, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 224)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.4.b. - Reports - Site Visits, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 225)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.5.a. - Financial - Provisional Reports, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 226)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.5.b. - Financial - Final Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 227)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.5.c. - Financial - Payments, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 228)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - B.6. - Audit Period B, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 229)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - A.1. - Correspondence - General (Box 24, Folder 230)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - A.2. - Proposal Year A (Box 24, Folder 231)
- New York Medical College (NYMC) - A.3. - Agreement Year A (Box 24, Folder 232)